A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Healthy Steps for Young Children Program, SG 2, Series 6 FA498
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Grants, 1991-2006; 4
  - Northwestern University - 980559 - Pediatric Development Services Program - Correspondence - Budetti, 1998 (Box 146, Folder 895)
  - Northwestern University - 980559 - Promoting Healthy Development in Medicaid Management Plans -, 1998-1999 (Box 146, Folder 896)
  - University of Oklahoma - Oklahoma City Bombing Effects on Children - 980309, 1998-2000 (Box 146, Folder 897)
  - Commonwealth Fund Parents Survey - Data Stat 95-37 - Administration & Budget, 1994-1996 (Box 146, Folder 898)
  - Commonwealth Fund Parents Survey - Data Stat 95-37 - Correspondence, 1995-1996 (Box 146, Folder 899)
  - Commonwealth Fund Parents Survey - Data Stat 95-37 - Draft Preliminary Findings, 1994-1996 (Box 147, Folder 900-903)
  - Commonwealth Fund Parents Survey - Data Stat 95-37 - Final Findings, 1996 (Box 147, Folder 904)
  - Commonwealth Fund Parents Survey - Data Stat 95-37 - Grant Products, 1995 (Box 147, Folder 905)
  - Parent Survey Meeting Materials, 1996 February 12 (Box 147, Folder 906)
  - Pediatrics Development Services Program - Program Plan, 1999 February 2 (Box 147, Folder 907)
  - Pediatric Development Services Program - Research Project - A Summary of Federally Funded Projects on Preventive and Developmental Services for Young Children, 1998 Sept. (Box 148, Folder 908)
  - University of Pennsylvania - Administration & Budget - Greater PA.- 9240, 1994 (Box 148, Folder 909)
  - University of Pennsylvania - Sponsor-A-Scholar - 93-85 - Administration and Budget, 1992-1997 (Box 148, Folder 910-911)
  - University of Pennsylvania - Sponsor-a-Scholar - 93-85 - Evaluation, 1993 Sept. 23 (Box 148, Folder 912)
  - University of Pennsylvania - Sponsor-a-Scholar - 93-85 - Evaluation, 1995-1996 (Box 148, Folder 913)
  - University of Pennsylvania - An Evaluation of the Impacts of the Sponsor-A-Scholar Program on Student Performance - Final Report, 1996 December (Box 148, Folder 914)
  - University of Pennsylvania - Proposal - 96593, 1996-1998 (Box 149, Folder 917)
  - Phipps Community College - 96758, 1996 (Box 149, Folder 918)
  - Princeton Survey Research Associates - 96919, 1996 (Box 149, Folder 919)
  - Public Private Ventures - 94-79 - Administration and Correspondence, 1990-1996 (Box 150, Folder 926-927)
  - Public Private Ventures - 94-79 - Grant Products, 1994-1995 (Box 150, Folder 928)
  - Public Private Ventures - 94-79 - Lessons Learned - HYMP, 1996-1997 (Box 150, Folder 929)
  - Public Private Ventures - 94-79 - Mentoring Youth - A Community Initiative, 1994-1996 (Box 150, Folder 930)
  - Public Private Ventures - 96621 - Phase 2, 1995-1997 (Box 150, Folder 931)
  - Public Private Ventures - The State and Future of Mentoring Conference - Plan - Fiscal Year 1996-1997, 970437, 1996-1997, 1999 (Box 151, Folder 933)
  - Robert Wood Johnson Foundation - Affiliate Evaluation, 1996-1998 (Box 151, Folder 934)
  - Robert Wood Johnson Foundation - A Proposal to Develop A Healthy Steps Multimedia Training Package, 1997 June 18 (Box 151, Folder 935)
  - Sponsor-A-Scholar - 96147 - Program, 1994-1997 (Box 151, Folder 936)
  - University of Wisconsin - Parenthood in America - Conference April 19-21, 1998 - 980327, 1997-1998 (Box 151, Folder 939)
  - Sponsor-A-Scholar - 95412 - Coalition of Community Foundations for Youth - Final Report, 1997-1999 (Box 151, Folder 938)
- Meetings, 1994-2005; 5
  Arranged in five subseries: 1. All Hands Meetings; 2. Board of Directors; 3. National Advisory Committee Meetings; 4. Local Advisory Committee; 5. Funders
  - All Hands Meeting, 1
    - All Hands Meeting, 1998 April 9 (Box 152, Folder 940)
    - All Hands Meeting, 1999 April 8 (Box 152, Folder 941)
    - All Hands Meeting, 1999 April 8 (Box 152, Folder 942)
    - All Hands Meeting, 1999 October 6 (Box 152, Folder 943)
    - All Hands Meeting, 2000 April 5 (Box 152, Folder 944)
    - All Hands Meeting, 2001 April 23 (Box 152, Folder 945)
  - Board of Directors, 2
    - Board Book Program - Youth, 1994 November (Box 152, Folder 946)
    - Board Book Pieces - Final, 1995 November (Box 152, Folder 947)
    - Board Final - Pieces, 1996 April (Box 152, Folder 948)
    - Board - Program Summary Youth, 1996 April (Box 153, Folder 949)
    - Board of Directors Talking Points & Meeting Notes - Children and Youth Department, 1996 Nov. 12 (Box 153, Folder 950)
    - Board Final, 1997-April (Box 153, Folder 951)
    - Board Final, 1997 July (Box 153, Folder 952)
    - Board - Healthy Steps Overview, 1997 Nov. (Box 153, Folder 953)
    - "Reinventing Pediatrics" Task Force - Jewish Healthcare Foundation - Pittsburgh, PA, 1997 June-Oct. (Box 153, Folder 954)
    - Board of Directors Site Visit - Briefing Material - Boston, MA., 1998 July 8-10 (Box 153, Folder 955)
    - Board Retreat - Revere Site Visit, 1998 July (Box 153, Folder 956)
    - Pediatric Development Services Program - Briefing Material - CWF, 1998 Dec. 15 (Box 154, Folder 957)
    - Pediatric Development Services Program - Briefing Material - Chicago, Illinois, 1998 July 15-18 (Box 154, Folder 958)
    - Planning Meeting for Healthy Steps - Possible Longitudinal Follow - Up Study - NY, 1999 Feb. 22 (Box 154, Folder 959)
    - Lessons Learned From A National Health Care Collaboration - Bringing Child Development Into Primary Care For Young Children - Colorado Island Marriott Resort, San Diego, CA, 2001 March 2 (Box 154, Folder 960)
    - Healthy Steps Site in Integrated Delivery Systems - Large Group and Staff Model HMO's - Third Progress Report - Seattle, WA., 2002 March (Box 154, Folder 961)
    - Management Meeting, 1995 Sept. 28 (Box 154, Folder 962)
    - Management Meeting, 1996 March 19 (Box 154, Folder 963)
    - Progress Report Meeting, 1997 April 18 (Box 154, Folder 964)
    - Program Review Meeting, 1997 April 18 (Box 155, Folder 965)
    - Program Coordination Meeting, 1997 July 9 (Box 155, Folder 966)
    - Program Monitoring Committee Meeting & The Commonwealth Fund Quarterly - Summer 1999 Vol. 5, Issue 2, 2000 June 14 (Box 155, Folder 967)
  - National Advisory Committee Meetings, 3
    - Briefing Book, 1996 May 23 (Box 155, Folder 968)
    - Task Force, 1996 May 23 (Box 155, Folder 969)
    - Bills, 1996 May-June (Box 155, Folder 970)
    - National Advisory Committee Meeting, 1996 Dec. 5-6 (Box 155, Folder 971)
    - Briefing Book, 1996 Dec.6 (Box 155, Folder 972)
    - BIU's/Set - Up - 12-6, 1996-19997 (Box 155, Folder 973)
    - National Advisory Committee Meeting, 1997 May 28 (Box 155, Folder 974)
    - National Advisory Committee Meeting, 1997 May 28 (Box 156, Folder 975)
    - National Advisory Committee Meeting, Briefing Book, 1997 October 29 (Box 156, Folder 976)
    - National Advisory Committee Meetings, 1997-1998 (Box 156, Folder 977)
    - Briefing Book, 1997 Dec. 17-18 (Box 156, Folder 978)
    - Briefing Book, 1998 May 26-27 (Box 156, Folder 979)
    - National Advisory Committee Meeting, 1997 May 26-27 (Box 157, Folder 980)
    - Briefing Book, 1998 Oct. 27-28 (Box 157, Folder 981)
    - National Advisory Committee Meeting, 1998 Oct. 27-28 (Box 157, Folder 982)
    - Briefing Book, 1999 May 25-26 (Box 157, Folder 983)
    - New York, 1999 May - Oct. (Box 157, Folder 984)
    - Briefing Book, 1999 June 14 (Box 157, Folder 985)
    - Briefing Book, 1999 Oct. 26-27 (Box 158, Folder 986)
    - Briefing Book, 1999 Dec. 17 (Box 158, Folder 987)
    - Briefing Book, 2000 Oct. 24-25 (Box 158, Folder 988)
    - Briefing Book, 2002 Oct. 24-25 (Box 158, Folder 989)
    - Briefing Book, 2001 Oct. 18-19 (Box 159, Folder 990)
    - National Multimedia Advisory Group Meeting, 1999 Dec. 17 (Box 159, Folder 991)
    - National Evaluation Team Meeting, 2000 Sept. 6 (Box 159, Folder 992)
  - Local Advisory Committees, 4
    - Local Advisory Committees, 1996-1998 (Box 159, Folder 993)
    - Local Advisory Committees, 1996-1998 (Box 159, Folder 994)
    - Local Advisory Committee - Selected Material From: Boston, MA., Grand Junction, CO., Kansas City, MO., Pittsburgh, PA, 1997 Oct. (Box 159, Folder 995)
    - Local Advisory Committees - Selected Information From: Chicago, Detroit, Grand Junction, Houston, Kansas City, Pittsburgh, San Antonio, 1998 (Box 160, Folder 996)
    - Local Advisory Committees - Selected Information From: Chicago, Detroit, Grand Junction, Houston, Kansas City, Pittsburgh, San Antonio, 1998 (Box 160, Folder 997)
  - Funders, 5
    - Disney: Correspondence, 1995-1997 (Box 160, Folder 998)
    - Funders, 1994-1996 (Box 160, Folder 999)
    - Funders, 1994-1996 (Box 160, Folder 1000)
    - Funders, 1994-1996 (Box 160, Folder 1001)
    - Insurance Funders, 1994-1997 (Box 161, Folder 1002)
    - Local Advisory Board Meeting - ABC Family Pediatrics Site - Allentown, PA., 2000 Feb. 17 (Box 161, Folder 1003)
    - Local Funder Network Meeting - Background Material - Temple Mission Palm Hotel, 1999 Feb. 17 (Box 161, Folder 1004)
    - Local Funder Network Meeting - Background Material - Hotel Inter-Continental - Miami, FL, 2000 March 1 (Box 161, Folder 1005)
    - Local Funder Network Meeting - Background Material - Waldorf Astoria Hotel, New York, NY, 2002 Feb. 26 (Box 161, Folder 1006)
    - Local Funder Network Meeting - Background Material - Century Plaza Hotel, Los Angeles, CA, 2003 Feb. 13 (Box 161, Folder 1007)
    - Local Funder Network Meeting - Background Material - The Westin Diplomat Resort and Spa. Hollywood, FL., 2004 Feb. 25 (Box 161, Folder 1008)
    - Local Funder Network Meeting - Background Material - Palace Hotel, San Francisco, CA, 2005 Feb. 23 (Box 161, Folder 1009)
- Working Papers, 1998-2001; 6
  - Assessing the Impact of Pediatric - Based Development Services on Infants, Families and Clinicians: Challenges to Evaluating the Healthy Steps Program - Working Paper Series - Vol. 1, No. 1, 1998 Sept. 18 (Box 162, Folder 1010)
  - Assessing the Impact of Pediatric - Based Developmental Services on Infants, Families and Clinicians: Challenges to Evaluating the Healthy Steps Program Vol. 1, No. 1, 1999 Feb. 12 (Box 162, Folder 1011)
  - A Profile of Healthy Steps National Evaluation Sites - Meeting the Needs of Very Young Children - Working Paper Series - Vol. 1, No. 2, 1998 March 5 (Box 162, Folder 1012)
  - A Profile of Healthy Steps National Evaluation Sites - Meeting the Needs of Very Young Children Vol. 1, No. 2, 1998 July 31 (Box 162, Folder 1013)
  - Baseline Key Informant Interviews - A Summary Report Vol. 1, No. 3, 1998 July 31 (Box 162, Folder 1014)
  - Baseline Key Informant Interviews - A Summary Report Vol. 1, No. 4, 1998 July 31 (Box 162, Folder 1015)
  - Baseline Provider Surveys - A Summary Report Vol. 1, No. 4, 1998 July 31 (Box 162, Folder 1016)
  - Methods for Determining Healthy Steps Costs for the Cost - Effectiveness Analysis - National Evaluation - Working Paper Series - Vol. 1, No. 5, 1999 Jan. 31 (Box 162, Folder 1017)
  - Methods for Determining Healthy Steps Cost for the Cost - Effectiveness Analysis - National Evaluation - Working Papers Series Vol. 1, No. 5, 1999 Jan. 31 (Box 162, Folder 1018)
  - Families at Baseline - A Summary of Newborn Form Data - Working Paper Series - Vol. 1, No. 6, 1999 June 15 (Box 162, Folder 1019)
  - Families at Baseline and Early Effects of H.S. at 2-4 Months - National Evaluation - Working Papers Series Vol. 1, No. 7 Draft, 1999 Oct. 1 (Box 162, Folder 1020)
  - Families at Baseline and Early Effects of Healthy Steps at 2-4 Months - National Evaluation - Working Paper Series Vol. 1, No. 7, 1999 Dec. 1 (Box 162, Folder 1021)
  - Families at Baseline and Early Effects of Healthy Steps at 2-4 Months - National Evaluation - Working Papers Series Vol. 1 No. 7, 1999 Dec. 1 (Box 163, Folder 1022)
  - Year One Cost Analysis - National Evaluation - Working Paper Series - Vol. 1, No. 8, 1999 Nov. 15 (Box 163, Folder 1023)
  - Families at 6 Months - A Summary of 6 Month Parent Questionnaire Data - National Evaluation Working Paper Series Vol. 1. No. 9, 2000 April 21 (Box 163, Folder 1024)
  - Families: The First Year - Summary of 12 Month Parent Questionnaire Data - National Evaluation Working Paper Series Vol. 1, No. 10, 2000 Nov. 30 (Box 163, Folder 1025)
  - Year Two Cost Analysis - National Evaluation Working Paper Series Vol. 2, No.1, 2000 Dec. 15 (Box 163, Folder 1026)
  - Program Services in the First Year of Life - A Summary of Healthy Steps Specialists' Contacts with Families - National Evaluation - Working Paper Series Vol. 2, No. 2, 2000 Feb.10 (Box 163, Folder 1027)
  - Families at 18 Months - Summary of 18 - Month Form Data - National Evaluation Working Paper Series Vol. 2, No. 3, 2001 May 24 (Box 163, Folder 1028)
  - Sustainability, Institutionalization and Related Concepts in the Context of Healthy Steps - National Evaluation Working Paper Series Vol. 2, No. 4, 2001 Dec. 15 (Box 163, Folder 1029)
  - Providers - Changes on Knowledge, Attitudes, and Practices - National Evaluation Working Paper Series Vol.2 No. 5, 2001 Dec. 15 (Box 163, Folder 1030)
  - Year Three Cost Analysis - National Evaluation Working Paper Series Vol. 2, No. 6, 2001 Dec. 15 (Box 164, Folder 1031)
  - Implementing Healthy Steps - Report From the Process Evaluation - National Evaluation Working Paper Series Vol. 2 No. 7, 2001 Dec. 15 (Box 164, Folder 1032)
- Program Reports, 1998-2003; 7
  - Families at Baseline and Early Effects of Healthy Steps at 2-3 Months: A Summary of Newborn Form and Parent Interview Data: Preliminary Sample - National Evaluation - Preliminary Report, 1998 November 6 (Box 164, Folder 1033-1036)
  - Families at Baseline and Early Effects of Healthy Steps at 2-3 Months: A Summary of Newborn Form and Parent Interview Data: Preliminary Sample - National Evaluation - Preliminary Report, 1998 November 6 (Box 165, Folder 1037)
  - Phase Three, Year One - Final Report, 1998 Feb. 6 (Box 165, Folder 1038)
  - Planner - Year II: Toddler and Preschool Training Institute - Boston University School of Medicine, 1998 May 29-31 (Box 165, Folder 1039-1040)
  - Year One - Final Report - Affiliated Evaluation, 1998 Nov. 13 (Box 165, Folder 1041)
  - Phase Three, Year Two - Final Report - National Evaluation - Vol. 1 of 2, 1999 March 1 (Box 166, Folder 1042)
  - Phase Three, Year Two - Final Report - National Evaluation Vol. 2 of 2, 1999 March 1 (Box 166, Folder 1043)
  - Planner - Year III Training Institute - Growing Up: Year III and Beyond, 1999 May 14 - 16 (Box 166, Folder 1044)
  - Year Two - Final Report - Affiliate Evaluation, 1999 Sept. 22 (Box 166, Folder 1045)
  - Phase Three, Year Three - Final Report - National Evaluation, 2000 February 15 (Box 166, Folder 1046)
  - Year Three - Final Report - Affiliate Evaluation, 2000 Sept. 8 (Box 166, Folder 1047)
  - Year One Office - Based Service Utilization and Cost Analysis - National Evaluation - Priliminary Report, 2000 Dec. 15 (Box 166, Folder 1048)
  - Phase Three, Year Four - Final Report - National Evaluation, 2001 Feb. 1 (Box 166, Folder 1049)
  - Child Development and Parenting Web Site Assessment - Interim Report - Assessment Methodology and Initial Findings, 2001 June 28 (Box 166, Folder 1050)
  - Distant Learning and the Healthy Steps for Young Children Program - Alternative Methods and Issues - Draft, 2002 Feb. (Box 166, Folder 1051)
  - Phase Three, Year Five - Final Report - National Evaluation, 2002 Feb. 1 (Box 166, Folder 1052)
  - The First Three Years - National Evaluation, 2003 Feb. 28 (Box 167, Folder 1053)
  - Final Report - Support for Program Direction and Operations - Contract #20020695, 2003 July 31 (Box 167, Folder 1054)
- Reports and Surveys, 1991-2002; 8
  - Building Blocks for Healthy Babies - Program Notebook, 1994 December (Box 167, Folder 1055)
  - Building Blocks for Healthy Babies - Program Notebook, 1994 December (Box 168, Folder 1056-1058)
  - Building Blocks for Healthy Babies - Program Binder - CWF, 1995 (Box 169, Folder 1059)
  - Career Academies - Manpower Demonstration Research Corporation, 1996 July (Box 169, Folder 1060)
  - Child Development and Parenting Web Site Assessment Interim Report - Assessment Methodology and Initial Findings, 2001 June 28 (Box 169, Folder 1061)
  - Child Health Chapter - Supporting Infants and Toddlers: The Nascent Policy Agenda - Kagan/Young -, 1998 (Box 169, Folder 1062)
  - Child Health Chapter - Supporting Infants and Toddlers: The Nascent Policy Agenda - Kagan/Young, 1997-1998 (Box 169, Folder 1063)
  - Child Rearing in America - The Conditions of Families with Young Children - Chapters 8-10, 2000 Nov. (Box 170, Folder 1064)
  - Child Rearing in America - The Conditions of Families with Young Children - Chapter 11-13, 2000 Nov. (Box 170, Folder 1065)
  - Child: The Essential Guide for Parents, 1998 Nov. (Box 170, Folder 1066)
  - Children Now, 1994-1996 (Box 170, Folder 1067)
  - Concept Paper - The Potential Additional Studies Using the Sample and Data From Healthy Steps - Conceptual, Methodological and Cost Issues, 1999 Aug. 20 (Box 170, Folder 1068)
  - Father to Father Program, 1996 (Box 170, Folder 1069)
  - The Greater Southeast School-To-Work - Transition Program, 1995-1996 (Box 171, Folder 1070)
  - Home Visiting, 1991-1994 (Box 171, Folder 1071)
  - Immunizations, 1994-1995 (Box 171, Folder 1072)
  - Implications of Healthy Steps Program for the Home Environment, Parent Child Interaction and Child Development, 1997-2002 (Box 171, Folder 1073)
  - Jobs for the Future - Hospital - Sponsored School-To-Work, 1995-1997 (Box 171, Folder 1074)
  - Johns Hopkins Evaluation of GSE - Greater Southeast Healthcare System, Phase 4, 1995-1997 (Box 171, Folder 1075)
  - Johns Hopkins Evaluation of GSE - Lewin Assessment GSE Report, 1995 (Box 171, Folder 1076)
  - Knowing and Doing - Connecting Learning and Work - Jobs for the Future, 1998 (Box 172, Folder 1077)
  - Material Depression, 1994-1995 (Box 172, Folder 1078)
  - Mc Manus Final Report Appendix: An Examination of Innovative Approaches for the Delivery & Financing of Parent Programs in Health Care Settings, 1995 Sept. (Box 172, Folder 1079)
  - National Center For Children in Poverty, 1994 (Box 172, Folder 1080)
  - National Organization on Adolescent Pregnancy, Parenting and Prevention, 1993-1994 (Box 172, Folder 1081)
  - Parenting - Healthy Steps Media Lists, 1996 (Box 172, Folder 1082)
  - Parenting - Issuesphere - 95-37, 1995-1997 (Box 172, Folder 1083)
  - Listening to Parents - Special Articles, Draft, 1996 (Box 172, Folder 1084)
  - Parent Survey - Advisory Group & Child Trends - Child Trends, 1995-1996 (Box 172, Folder 1085)
  - Parent Survey Analysis - KD, 1996 (Box 173, Folder 1086)
  - Parent Survey - Charles Novitz - Media Training and Communications - Issuesphere 95-37, 1995-1996 (Box 173, Folder 1087)
  - Parent Survey - Contract and Cross Tabs & Banners 95-37, 1994-1995 (Box 173, Folder 1088)
  - Parent Survey - Data Stat - Data Runs and Data Stat AAP paper 12-30-96 - 95-37, 1995-1996 (Box 173, Folder 1089)
  - Parent Survey - Executive Summary, 1996 (Box 173, Folder 1090)
  - Parent Survey - Files - Margins on Data, Survey Sample, Schedule, Survey Meeting and Tabs & Banner Points, 1994-1996 (Box 173, Folder 1091)
  - Parents Survey - Media Coverage, 1996-1997 (Box 173, Folder 1092)
  - Parent Survey - National Survey of Parents with Children from Birth to Age Three - Appendix, 1996 (Box 174, Folder 1093)
  - Parent Survey Notes, 1996 (Box 174, Folder 1094)
  - Parent Survey - Review - Parenting Infants - Child Trends, K. Moore, 1994-1998 (Box 174, Folder 1095)
  - Parent Survey - Report on the Findings, 1996 June 21 (Box 174, Folder 1096)
  - Parenting Experts Meeting, 1994 Sept. 21 (Box 174, Folder 1097)
  - Princeton Survey Research Associates on Behalf of The CWF - Successful Mentoring Relationships, 1998 May 22 (Box 174, Folder 1098)
  - Promising Practices: A Study of Ten School - to - Career Programs - Jobs for the Future, 1995 (Box 174, Folder 1099)
  - ROR - Reach Out and Read - New York City, 1996-1997 (Box 175, Folder 1100)
  - Relationships in Career Mentoring Program - Lessons Learned from Hospital Youth Mentoring Program, 1998 Sept (Box 175, Folder 1101)
  - Smart Start, 1993-1994 (Box 175, Folder 1102)
  - Strategies for Change - Child Development in Primary Care for Young Children, 1999 (Box 175, Folder 1103)
  - Strategies for Change - Child Development in Primary Care for Young Children, 1999 (Box 175, Folder 1104)
  - Survey of Parents - Draft Chapters - 970654, 1999 Jan.- Feb. (Box 176, Folder 1106)
  - Survey of Parents - Draft Chapters - 970654, 1998-1999 (Box 176, Folder 1105)
  - Survey of Parents - Draft Chapters - 970654, 1999 February-May (Box 176, Folder 1107)
  - Survey of Parents - Draft Chapters - 970654, 1999 June (Box 176, Folder 1108)
  - Survey of Parents - Draft Chapters - 970654, 1999 July-August (Box 176, Folder 1109)
  - Survey of Parents - Draft Chapters - 970654, 1999 August (Box 177, Folder 1110)
  - Survey of Parents - Draft Chapters - 970654, 1999 September-October (Box 177, Folder 1111)
  - Survey of Parents - Draft Chapters - 970654, 1999 November-December (Box 177, Folder 1112)
  - Survey of Parents - Draft Chapters - 970654, 2000 (Box 177, Folder 1113)
  - Survey of Parents with Children Under Three - Weighted - Final, Book 1, 1995 July - 1996 Jan. (Box 177, Folder 1114)
  - Survey of Parents with Children Under Three - Weighted - Final, Book 2, 1995 July - 1996 Jan.. (Box 178, Folder 1115)
  - Survey of Parents with Children Under Three - Weighted - Final, Book 3, 1995 July - 1996 Jan. (Box 178, Folder 1116)
  - Survey of Parents with Young Children - Media, 1996 (Box 178, Folder 1117)
  - Survey of Parents - Report on the Findings 1 of 2, 1995-1996 (Box 178, Folder 1118)
  - Survey of Parents - Report on the Findings 2 of 2, 1995-1996 (Box 178, Folder 1119)
  - Survey of Parents - Final Report, 1996 June 21 (Box 179, Folder 1120)
  - Survey Presentations 95-37, 1996-1997 (Box 179, Folder 1121)
  - Survey Presentations - Media Advisory and Parents 95-37, 1996 (Box 179, Folder 1122)
  - Teenage Child Bearing - Child Trends Study, 1993 (Box 179, Folder 1123)
  - The Hospital Youth Mentoring Network - Program In A Box - A Complete Resource Kit, 1997 (Box 179, Folder 1124)
  - Work It - Assessing Experience - The Hospital Youth Mentoring Network, 1997 (Box 179, Folder 1125)
  - Work It - Career Discovery Through Mentoring - The Hospital Youth Mentoring Network, 1997 (Box 179, Folder 1126)
  - Work It - Connecting Program Parents - The Hospital Youth Mentoring Network, 1997 (Box 179, Folder 1127)
  - Work It - Sustaining On the Job Learning - The Hospital Youth Mentoring Network, 1997 (Box 179, Folder 1128)
  - Youth - Survey of Young African Americans - CWF, 1994 (Box 179, Folder 1129)
  - Youth - Dropping Out of High School: A Pilot Survey of Young African Males in Four Cities - Study 902066, 1994 (Box 180, Folder 1130)
  - Pilot Survey of Young African-American Males in Four Cities, 1994 December 8 (Box 180, Folder 1131)
  - Young African-American Male Survey, 1997 Feb. 10 (Box 180, Folder 1132)
  - Young African-American Male Survey, 1997 February 10 (Box 180, Folder 1133)
  - Youth Sports - Carnegie, 1993-1996 (Box 180, Folder 1134)
- Publications, 1985-1998; 9
  - Investing in Our Children - Business and The Public Schools, 1985 (Box 180, Folder 1135)
  - Caring for Our Future - The Content of Parental Care - A Report of the Public Health Service Expert Panel on the Content of Parental Care, 1989 (Box 180, Folder 1136)
  - Children in Need - Investment Strategis for the Educationally Disadvantaged, 1989 (Box 180, Folder 1137)
  - Reducing Child Maltreatment Among High-Risk Families, 1989 May (Box 180, Folder 1138)
  - Quality Preschool Programs - A Long-Term Social Investment, 1989 June (Box 181, Folder 1139)
  - The Future of Child Health in New York City, 1989 Aug. (Box 181, Folder 1140)